corkin.com 2013-11-22

# Post an Ad - Corkin - Corkin - Free Classifieds Free Ads - Free Local Classifieds local and Nationwide. Jobs Search, Used car, Golf clubs, NBA or WWE tickets, auto insurance, dwi, dui, Pet Classifieds, Sell a Car, Sell a Timeshare, sell textbooks, Buy Laptops, IT Jobs, sell my car, Buy DVD, buy a dog, Sell Used car, Sell my House. Find Friends. Car listings, Motorcycles For Sale, Real Estate listings, apartmanets for rent, Job Listings, Post Resume, Find People, Online Jobs, vacation rentals, and personals sales

Privacy Policy - Corkin - Corkin - Free Classifieds Free Ads - Free Local Classifieds local and Nationwide. Jobs Search, Used car, Golf clubs, NBA or WWE tickets, auto insurance, dwi, dui, Pet Classifieds, Sell a Car, Sell a Timeshare, sell textbooks, Buy Laptops, IT Jobs, sell my car, Buy DVD, buy a dog, Sell Used car, Sell my House. Find Friends. Car listings, Motorcycles For Sale, Real Estate listings, apartmanets for rent, Job Listings, Post Resume, Find People, Online Jobs, vacation rentals, and personals sales

## Welcome to  Corkin.com

### **Privacy Policy**

Corkin has established this privacy policy to explain to you how your information is protected, collected and used, which may be updated by Corkin from time to time. Corkin will provide notice of materially significant changes to this privacy policy by posting notice on the Corkin site. 

#### 1\. Protecting your privacy 

  * We don't share your information with third parties for marketing purposes.  

  * Account information is password-protected. Keep your password safe. 

  * Corkin use cookies for authentication. Click on the log out link to log out. 

  * Corkin does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13. If Corkin learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 13, Corkin will remove that post. 

  * Corkin, or people who post on Corkin, may provide links to third party websites, which may have different privacy practices. We are not responsible for, nor have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website visited. 

#### 2\. Data we collect 

  * We sometimes collect your email address, for purposes such as sending self-publishing and confirmation emails, authenticating user accounts, providing subscription email services, registering for forums, etc. 

  * We may collect personal information if you provide it in feedback or comments, post it on our classifieds or interactive forums, or if you contact us directly. Please do not post any personal information on Corkin's forums or classifieds that you expect to keep private. 

  * Our web logs collect standard web log entries for each page served, including your IP address, page URL, and timestamp. Web logs help us to diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Corkin site, and to otherwise provide our service to you. 

#### 3\. Data we store 

  * All classified and forum postings are stored in our database, even after "deletion," and may be archived elsewhere. 

  * Our web logs and other records are stored indefinitely. 

  * Users can access and update their account information through the users account homepage. 

  * Although we make good faith efforts to store the information in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security. 

#### 4\. Archiving and display of Corkin postings by search engines and other sites 

Search engines and other sites not affiliated with Corkin - including _[archive.org](http://archive.org/)_ , [google.com](http://google.com/), and [yahoo.com](http://www.yahoo.com/) \- archive or otherwise make available Corkin postings and listings 

#### 5\. Circumstances in which Corkin may release information 

  * Corkin may disclose information about its users if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. 

  * Corkin may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our _[Terms of Use](http://www.corkin.com/includes/TermsOfUse.cfm)_ ; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Corkin, its users or the general public. 

#### 6\. International Users 

By visiting our web site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of Corkin we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, please understand that such data may be stored on servers located in the United States. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data. 

#### 7\. Feedback 

We welcome your feedback on this document in our _[Corkin forum](http://www.corkin.com/forums/viewForum.cfm?fid=14&ForumName=Corkin)_  .
